Franz Boas Papers 1862-1942 Mss.B.B61.inventory6 Mss.B.B61.inventory06
American Philosophical Society
- Franz Boas Papers - Correspondents H
  - Herrey, H. (Box 39)
    - From Boas, 1941 July 28; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 Nov. 21; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1941 July 17; 1p.
  - Herrick (Box 39)
    - Herrick -- to Hodge, 1899 Apr. 8
  - Herring, H.C. (Box 39)
    - From Boas, 1930 Sept. 11; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 Sept. 24; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 Oct. 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Sept. 10; 1p.
    - (Enc: Preliminary statement of the American Interracial Seminar and its national committee.), 1930 Sept. 25; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Oct. 14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 July 2; 3p.
      (Enc: re American Interracial Seminar)
  - Herring, John A. (Box 39)
    - To Boas, 1919 Oct. 30; 1p.
  - Herrman, Esther (Box 39)
    - From Boas, 1898 Dec. 6; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1907 Nov. 13
    - From Boas, 1908 June 11
    - From Boas, 1908 June 11
    - From Boas, 1908 June 19
    - From Boas, 1908 Oct. 15
    - From Boas, 1908 Oct. 26
    - From Boas, 1909 May 27; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1908 Oct. 16
    - To Boas, 1908 Oct. 23
  - Herron, Emily K. (Box 39)
    - To Boas, 1907 Oct. 14
    - To Boas, 1907 Oct. 25
    - To Boas, 1909 Apr. 20
    - To Boas, 1909 Nov. 13
  - Hershey, A.H. (Box 39)
    - To Boas, 1899 July 15
    - To Boas, 1899 Sept. 25
    - To Boas, 1900 Sept. 29
    - To Boas, 1912 Dec. 17
    - To Boas, 1917 May 17
    - A.H. Hershey -- to H.A. Andrews, 1913 May 24
  - Herskovits, Mel J. (Box 39)
    - From Boas, 1925 Mar. 10; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1925 Apr. 13; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1926 July 20; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 Sept. 21; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 Nov. 1; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1927 Nov. 15; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 Nov. 23; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 Dec. 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 Jan. 30; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 Jan. 31; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1928 June 2; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 Nov. 12; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1928 Nov. 16; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1928 Nov. 19; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 Nov. 26; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1928 Dec. 3; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1928 Dec. 6; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1928 Dec. 11; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Jan. 25; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Apr. 19; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 May 8; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 May 8; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Nov. 26; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 Jan. 6; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 May 12; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 May 14; telegram
    - From Boas, 1930 May 15; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 June 12; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Nov. 4; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Dec. 4; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Dec. 10; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1932 Apr. 5; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1932 Oct. 31; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 Oct. 19; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 Nov. 28; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 Sept. 12; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1935 Feb. 21; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1935 Mar. 4; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1935 Mar. 11; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1935 Apr. 10; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1935 May 4; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1935 June 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 Feb. 11; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 May 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 Nov. 24; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1937 Dec. 20; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1941 June 13; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1942 Oct. 19; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1942 Nov. 2; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1942 Nov. 11; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1923 June 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1924 Oct. 20; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1925 Feb. 5; 1p.
    - (Enc: Rae, P.M. to Herskovits, M.J. Feb. 2, 1925), 1925 Feb. 11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1925 Mar. 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1925 Apr. 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1925 May 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1926 July 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1926 July 23; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Jan. 4; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1927 June 29; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 July 14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Aug. 31; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Oct. 10; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Nov. 9; 2p.
    - (Enc: Chart), 1927 Nov. 23; 1p.
    - (Enc: Chart), 1927 Dec. 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Dec. 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Jan. 25; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Jan. 25-30; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 June 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Oct. 22; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Nov. 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Nov. 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Nov. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Dec. 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Dec. 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Jan. 2; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Jan. 22; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Feb. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Mar. 4; 1p.
    - (Enc: Roth, W.E. to Herskovits, M.J. Feb. 10, 1929), 1929 May 1; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 May 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Oct. 5; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Oct. 28; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Nov. 2; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Dec. 2; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Dec. 23; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 May 14; telegram
    - To Boas, 1930 May 22; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 June 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Jan. 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Apr. 7; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Apr. 18; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1931 May 31; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 July 29; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Oct. 29; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Nov. 11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Dec. 1; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Apr. 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Sept. 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Nov. 3; 1p.
    - See Boas, F. (open letter) Jan. 27, 1933., 1933 Feb. 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Apr. 10; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Sept. 6; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Nov. 23; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Dec. 1; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Dec. 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Oct. 24; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Nov. 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 Jan. 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 Feb. 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 Feb. 28; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 Mar. 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 Mar. 29; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 Apr. 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 June 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 June 25; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 June 25; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Feb. 11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Mar. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Apr. 28; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 June 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Sept. 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Nov. 17; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Dec. 23; 1p.
    - (Enc: Herskovits, M.J. to Augustin, J.J. Dec. 23, 1936), 1937 Mar. 27; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Dec. 30; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1938 Apr. 28; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1938 Aug. 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Apr. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 May 23; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 June 23; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 July 23; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1941 Mar. 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1942 Oct. 26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1942 Nov. 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1942 Nov. 14; 1p.
    - M.J. Herskovits -- to J.J. Augustin, 1936 Dec. 23; 1p.
    - (Enc. with Herskovits, N.J., Dec. 23,1936)
    - M.J. Herskovits -- to H.R. Bryan, 1933 Apr. 10; 1p.
    - M.J. Herskovits -- from M.C. Kahn, 1928 Jan. 25
    - M.J. Herskovits -- to E.C. Parsons, 1937 Aug. 30; 1p.
    - M.J. Herskovits -- from P.M. Rae, 1925 Feb. 2
    - (Enc. originally in Herskovits, M.J., Feb. 5, 1925)
    - M.J. Herskovits -- from W.E. Roth, 1929 Feb. 10
    - (Enc. originally with Herskovits, M.J., Mar. 4, 1929)
    - M.J. Herskovits -- from George Saslow, 1936 July 5
  - Herskovits, M.J. and F.S. (Box 39)
    - See enc. Boas, F. to Moe, H.A., Dec. 31, 1936
  - Herskovitz (Box 39)
    - See American Council of Learned Societies, 1937 Feb. 15
  - Hertwig, R. (Box 39)
    - To Boas, 1925 July 30; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1925 Sept. 10; 2p.
  - Hertz, Friedrich (Box 39)
    - From Boas, 1923 Apr. 4; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1923 June 23; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1923 Mar. 21; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1923 June 15; 2p.
  - Hertz, Helen (Box 39)
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 19; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1960 Mar. 19; 2p.
  - Hertz, Rudolf (Box 39)
    - From Boas, 1936 June 2; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1939 Oct. 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Feb. 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Feb. 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Sept. 23; 1p.
    - R. Hertz -- from G.L. Nute, 1932 Mar. 16
    - R. Hertz -- to M.W. Stirling, 1936 June 13; 1p.
  - Hertzka, Y. (Box 39)
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 14; 1p.
  - Hervey, William A. (Box 39)
    - From Boas, 1913 Feb. 24
    - To Boas, 1909 Jan. 8
    - To Boas, 1909 Feb. 6; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1911 May 1
    - W.A. Hervey -- to A.B. Belaski, 1917 Nov. 3; 2p.
    - W.A. Hervey -- to Wilson, Woodrow(Pres. of U.S.), 1917 Nov. 27
  - Hervey (Registrar, Columbia University) (Box 39)
    - From Boas, 1909 Jan. 29; 1p.
  - Herz, Julius (Box 39)
    - From Boas, 1939 Jan. 26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Jan. 24; 1p.
  - Herzog, George (Box 39)
    - From Boas, 1926 June 30; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Jan. 14; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Apr. 9; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Apr. 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 May 1; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 May 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 May 10; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Oct. 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Oct. 14; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Oct. 16; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 June 20; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Dec. 14; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1932 Jan. 12; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1932 May 31; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1932 Oct. 20; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1932 Dec. 19; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 Apr. 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 Apr. 28; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 May 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 May 28; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 Sept. 27; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1935 Feb. 12; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 Apr. 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1939 Oct. 2; 1p.
    - See Boas, F. (open letter) Nov. 6, 1941, 1942 Feb. 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1926 June 27; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1926 July 4; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1927 July 13; 5p.
    - To Boas, 1927 July 26; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Sept. 9; 3p.
    - See Boas, F. (open letter) Nov. 10, 1927, 1928 July 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Apr. 11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Apr. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 May 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 May 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Aug. 19; 5p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Oct. 7; 7p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Oct. 28; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Nov. 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Feb. 14; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Apr. 14; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1930 May 2; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Aug. 3; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Aug. 14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Mar.
    - To Boas, 1931 Apr. 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 May 10; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Jan. 14; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Jan. 16; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Jan. 17; telegram
    - To Boas, 1932 June 2; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Oct. 25; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Dec. 12; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Jan. 11; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Apr. 17; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Apr. 19; 2p.
    - (Enc: List of Upper Chehalis phonograph records...), 1933 Apr. 24; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1933 May 26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 June 5; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Sept. 26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Dec. 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 June 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Sept. 24; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Sept. 28; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Oct. 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Oct. 29; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Dec. 14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 Apr. 17; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Feb. 28; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Feb. 28; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Mar. 11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Mar. 25; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Mar. 30; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Apr. 13; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1937 May 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Apr. 18; 1p.
    - (Enc. with Herzog, G. Apr. 18, 1939), 1939 Apr. 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 July 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 Feb.
    - (See Amer. Folklore Society Feb. 1940), 1940 Aug. 11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1941 Sept. 13; 1p.
    - G. Herzog -- from L.C. Goodrich, 1929 Nov. 1
    - (Enc. with Goodrich, L.C., Nov. 1, 1929.)
  - Herzog, Wilhelm P. (Box 39)
    - To Boas, 1891; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1894 Dec. 17
  - Heschel, Abraham (Box 39)
    - From Boas, 1940 Sept. 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 Sept. 11; 2p.
  - Hess, Alfred F. (Box 39)
    - From Boas, 1919 Apr. 8; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Apr. 25; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1919 May 12; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1919 May 16; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1919 July 14; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 26; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 11; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1921 Mar. 9; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1923 Jan. 17; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1923 Feb. 12; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1923 Oct. 23; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1925 Feb. 25; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Jan. 14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1922 Dec. 22; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1923 Jan. 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1923 Oct. 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1925 Mar. 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Jan. 17; 1p.
  - Hess, Mrs. Alfred F. (Box 39)
    - From Boas, 1931 May 6; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1935 Nov. 11; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1935 Nov. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 Nov. 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 Nov. 19; 2p.
  - Hess, Leo (Box 39)
    - To Boas, 1941 Dec. 30; postcard
  - Hestermann, F. (Box 39)
    - From Boas, 1925 July 21; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 Feb. 14; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 Jan. 23; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 Oct. 20; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Apr. 29; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1925 July 8; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1925 Aug. 25; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Jan. 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Oct. 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Jan. 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Apr. 24; 2p.
  - Hete (Box 39)
    - To Boas, 1939 Aug. 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Aug. 17; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Aug. 24; 1p.
  - Hetzel, Victor L. (Box 39)
    - From Boas, 1932 Apr. 20; 1p.
  - Heubsch, B.W. (Box 39)
    - From Boas, 1920 Aug. 11; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Sept. 14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Aug. 9; 1p.
  - B.W. Heubsch, Inc. (Box 39)
    See The Freeman, Inc.
    See Sniton, H.
  - Heuser (Box 39)
    - To Boas, 1920 Feb. 28; 6p.
  - Heuser, Frederick W.J. (Box 39)
    - From Boas, 1920 June 4; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 July 19; 1p.
    - (Enc: Letter dated July 16, 1920 from Boas, F. & Heuser, F.W.J. to Speyer, James), 1920 July 21; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 July 31; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Aug. 2; 1p.
    - (Enc: Draft of report - Emergency Society in Aid of European Science and Art), 2p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Aug. 6; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Aug. 17; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Aug. 23; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Sept. 8; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Sept. 20; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 13; 1p.
    - See Boas, F. to Klenze, C. v., Nov. 24, 1920.
    - See Boas, F. to Speyer, J. Nov. 29, 1920., 1920 Dec. 22; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1922 Nov. 11; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1922 Nov. 15; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1922 Nov. 27; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1922 Dec. 14; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1922 Dec. 22; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1923 Jan. 15; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1923 Feb. 5; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1923 Mar. 9; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Mar. 12; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Nov. 4; 1p.
    - (Enc: Heuser, F.W.J. Dec. 15, 1928), 1935 Nov. 14; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1935 Dec. 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 July 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 July 23; 1p.
    - (Encls: Sample letterhead Rough draft for letterheads for Emergency Society in Aid of European Science and Art), 1920 July 30; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Aug. 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Aug. 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Aug. 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Aug. 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Aug. 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Sept. 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Sept. 17; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 14; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 22; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 29; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Nov. 23; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Dec.; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1922 Nov. 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1922 Nov. 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1922 Nov. 23; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1922 Dec. 6; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1922 Dec. 27; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1923 Jan. 20; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1923 June 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Feb. 23; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Dec. 15; 1p.
    - (Enc: List. Enc. originally with Boas, F. to Heuser F.W.J. Nov. 4, 1929), 1929 Mar. 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Oct. 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Apr. 15; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1931 July 2; 3p.
    - (Enc: Award of Germanistic Society stipends...), 1932 Jan. 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 Nov. 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 Nov. 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 Dec. 2; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1935 Dec. 10; 1p.
    - F.W.J. Heuser -- from Frederick M. Allen, 1923 Feb. 9; 1p.
    - F.W.J. Heuser -- to Betz, 1922 Dec. 6; 2p.
    - F.W.J. Heuser -- to Ruth W. Bryan, 1940 Jan. 19; 1p.
    - F.W.J. Heuser -- from Ernst Danziger, 1923 Feb. 13; 1p.
    - (Enc: Letter from Schwalbe, J. to Einhorn, dated 1-17-23)
    - F.W.J. Heuser -- from R.A. Gortner, 1923 Jan. 8; 1p.
    - F.W.J. Heuser -- from R.A. Gortner, 1923 Jan. 8; 1p.
    - F.W.J. Heuser -- to Mmebers of the Germanistic Society of America, 1931 Nov. 16; 1p.
    - F.W.J. Heuser -- to F.M. Pendreigh, 1920 Dec. 9; 1p.
    - F.W.J. Heuser -- to J.C. Robbins, 1923 Mar. 2; 1p.
    - F.W.J. Heuser -- to Schmidt Ott, F., 1931 Dec. 8; 1p.
      (Enc: 2 lists)
    - F.W.J. Heuser & Boas, F. -- to James Speyer, 1920 July 16; 1p.
    - F.W.J. Heuser -- from G. Steinhagen, 1923 Feb. 26; 2p.
    - F.W.J. Heuser -- from W.K. Thomas, 1932 Jan. 16
    - F.W.J. Heuser -- from Anna Urbach, 1923 June 13; 1p.
    - F.W.J. Heuser -- from Anna Urbach, 1923 June 18; 1p.
  - Heuser, Dr. G. (Box 39)
    - From Boas, 1931 Feb. 16; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Feb. 27; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Dec. 29; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Feb. 17; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Feb. 17; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Feb. 26; 2p.
  - Hewett, Edgar Lee (Box 39)
    - From Boas, 1907 Apr. 22
    - From Boas, 1907 May 8
    - From Boas, 1907 May 18
    - From Boas, 1907 May 23
    - From Boas, 1907 May 25
    - From Boas, 1907 Aug. 9
    - From Boas, 1908 Mar. 13
    - From Boas, 1911 Nov. 13
    - To Boas, 1907 Apr.
    - To Boas, 1907 Apr. 20
    - To Boas, 1907 Apr. 25
    - To Boas, 1907 May 2
    - To Boas, 1907 May 11
    - To Boas, 1907 May 16
    - To Boas, 1907 May 17
    - To Boas, 1907 May 18
    - To Boas, 1907 May 20
    - To Boas, 1907 May 23
    - To Boas, 1907 May 31
    - To Boas, 1907 June 7
    - To Boas, 1908 Apr. 30; 2p.
    - E.L. Hewett -- to C.P. Bowditch, 1906 Jan. 16
    - E.L. Hewett -- to Com. of General Land Office, 1904 Sept. 14; 7p.
    - E.L. Hewett -- from F.W. Putnam, 1906 Feb. 8
  - Hewett, W.T. (Box 39)
    - From Boas, 1905 Nov. 17; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1905 Nov. 25; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1906 Mar. 5; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1906 Mar. 13; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1906 Mar. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1905 Nov. 18; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1905 Dec. 23; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1906 Feb. 27; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1906 Mar. 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1906 Mar. 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1906 Mar. 17; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1906 Mar. 27; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1906 Apr. 16; 2p.
  - Hewitt (Box 39)
    - See Denig manuscript enc. with Denig, R., Sept. 8, 1924.
  - Hewitt, John Napoleon Brinton (Box 39)
    - From Boas, 1907 Aug. 30; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1907 Nov. 9
    - From Boas, 1907 Nov. 18
    - To Boas, 1907 Nov. 16
    - To Boas, 1907 Nov. 23
    - To Boas, 1917 Nov. 10
    - J.N.B. Hewitt -- to W.H. Holmes, 1908 Jan. 29
  - Hewson (Box 39)
  - Hexamer, C.J. (Box 40)
    - From Boas, 1907 Aug. 31; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1907 Sept. 27; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1907 Oct. 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1907 Aug. 26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1907 Sept. 23; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1907 Oct. 19; 1p.
    - C.J. Hexamer -- to Herman Ridder, 1914 June 2; 1p.
  - Heydner, Rolf (Box 40)
    - From Boas, 1923 Feb. 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1923 Feb. 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1923 Mar. 7; 1p.
  - Heydrick, M. (Box 40)
    - To Boas, 1927 Nov. 27; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 June 28; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1929 July 29; 1p.
  - Heydt, Herman A. (Box 40)
    - From Boas, 1942 Feb. 11; 1p.
  - Heye, George G. (Box 40)
    - From Boas, 1906 Feb. 17
    - From Boas, 1906 Mar. 28
    - From Boas, 1906 June 5
    - From Boas, 1906 June 8
    - From Boas, 1906 June 12
    - From Boas, 1906 Aug. 31
    - From Boas, 1906 Oct. 2
    - From Boas, 1906 Nov. 8
    - From Boas, 1906 Nov. 16
    - From Boas, 1906 Dec. 6
    - From Boas, 1906 Dec. 18
    - From Boas, 1907 Jan. 11
    - From Boas, 1907 Feb. 7
    - From Boas, 1907 Feb. 14
    - From Boas, 1907 Mar. 6
    - From Boas, 1907 Mar. 8
    - From Boas, 1907 Mar. 20
    - From Boas, 1907 Mar. 23
    - From Boas, 1907 Apr. 1
    - From Boas, 1907 Apr. 3
    - From Boas, 1907 Apr. 22
    - From Boas, 1907 Apr. 24
    - From Boas, 1907 Apr. 27
    - From Boas, 1907 Apr. 30
    - From Boas, 1907 Aug. 9
    - From Boas, 1907 Aug. 26
    - From Boas, 1907 Oct. 8
    - From Boas, 1907 Dec. 17
    - From Boas, 1907 Dec. 17
    - From Boas, 1907 Dec. 21
    - From Boas, 1908 Jan. 22
    - From Boas, 1908 Apr. 1
    - From Boas, 1908 Apr. 6
    - From Boas, 1908 Apr. 16
    - From Boas, 1908 May 23
    - From Boas, 1910 Jan. 11; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1910 Apr. 25; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1911 May 3; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1911 May 6
    - From Boas, 1912 Nov. 20; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1913 Oct. 21
    - From Boas, 1913 Nov. 17; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1914 Jan. 15
    - From Boas, 1915 Jan. 2; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1915 Jan. 5
    - From Boas, 1915 Jan. 22; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1915 Nov. 23; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1916 Jan. 7; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1916 Sept. 27
    - From Boas, 1916 Oct. 11; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1916 Oct. 31
    - From Boas, 1916 Dec. 13; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1918 Mar. 4; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Sept. 14; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 8; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 12; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1926 Jan. 4; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1926 Feb. 1; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1926 June 14; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 Mar. 2; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 Nov. 30; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1935 Apr. 25; 1p.
    - To Boas
    - See Boas, F. June 12, 1905, 1906 June 7
    - To Boas, 1906 June 11
    - To Boas, 1906 July 26
    - To Boas, 1906 July 30
    - To Boas, 1906 Aug. 20
    - To Boas, 1906 Sept. 4
    - To Boas, 1906 Oct. 4
    - To Boas, 1906 Oct. 25
    - To Boas, 1906 Dec. 17
    - To Boas, 1907 Jan. 14
    - To Boas, 1907 Feb. 13
    - To Boas, 1907 Feb. 15
    - To Boas, 1907 Mar. 7
    - To Boas, 1907 Mar. 21
    - To Boas, 1907 Mar. 25
    - To Boas, 1907 Apr. 2
    - To Boas, 1907 Apr. 23
    - To Boas, 1907 May 2
    - To Boas, 1907 Aug. 12
    - To Boas, 1907 Aug. 23
    - To Boas, 1907 Aug. 28
    - To Boas, 1907 Oct. 9
    - To Boas, 1907 Dec. 18
    - To Boas, 1907 Dec. 24
    - To Boas, 1908 Jan. 24
    - To Boas, 1908 Apr. 6; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1908 Apr. 21; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1908 May 26; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1910 Mar. 7; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1911 May 5
    - To Boas, 1911 May 8
    - To Boas, 1913 Oct. 22
    - To Boas, 1913 Nov. 5
    - To Boas, 1914 Feb. 3
    - To Boas, 1915 Jan. 4
    - To Boas, 1915 Nov. 29
    - To Boas, 1916 Jan. 10
    - To Boas, 1916 Dec. 8
    - To Boas, 1916 Dec. 14
    - To Boas, 1918 Mar. 2; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Dec. 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Dec. 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Mar. 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Dec. 2; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Apr. 17; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 Apr. 26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 May 29; 1p.
    - G.G. Heye -- from N.M. Butler, 1916 Dec. 22
    - G.G. Heye -- from N.M. Butler, 1916 Dec. 22
    - G.G. Heye -- from N.M. Butler, 1927 May 20
    - (Enc. with Butler, N.M., May 20, 1927)
    - G.G. Heye -- from B. Oetteking, 1925 Nov. 7
    - (Enc. with Oetteking, B., Nov. 10, 1925)
    - G.G. Heye -- to B. Oetteking, 1925 Nov. 9; 1p.
    - (Enc. with Oetteking, B., Nov. 10, 1925)
  - Heye Foundation - Museum of the American Indian (Box 40)
    - To Boas, 1930 July 29; 1p.
    - (Enc: James Paytiamo to Bureau (i.e. Museum) of American Indians -, July 14, 1930)
  - Heym, Stefan (Box 40)
    - From Boas, 1937 Apr. 5; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1937 Apr. 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Apr. 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 July 10; 1p.
  - Heyman, David M. (Box 40)
    - From Boas, 1935 Sept. 26; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1935 Sept. 30; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1935 Oct. 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Mar. 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 Sept. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 Oct. 1; 1p.
    - D.M. Heyman -- to J.J. Weinstein, 1934 Sept. 18; 1p.
    - (Enc. with Weinstein, J.J., Sept. 18,1934)
  - Heysinger, I.W. (Box 40)
    - I.W. Heysinger -- to W.H. Holmes, 1904 Oct. 26; 5p.
  - Heyward, J.S. (Box 40)
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 6; 1p.
  - Hibbard, A. (Box 40)
    - From Boas, 1936 Jan. 2; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 Dec. 23; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Jan. 6; 1p.
  - Hibbitt, G.W. (Box 40)
    - From Boas, 1936 May 18; 1p.
  - Hickok, R.K. (Box 40)
    - To Boas, 1940 Dec. 5; telegram
  - Hilbers, Henry (Box 40)